Samuel W.S. Fan

Full Stack Developer

Samuel Fan

3222 W 30th Ave.

Denver, CO 80211-3617

Contact

303.725.6329

samisfan@msn.com

LinkedIn Github Portfolio

—

Summary

Full Stack Developer

Experience as an architect in the AEC (Architecture, Engineering, Construction) industry

Experience with: project management, client communication, team collaboration

Full Stack Bootcamp Certificate of Completion

Skills and Projects

Dev languages: React, JavaScript, Express, jQuery, HTML, CSS, MongoDB, MySQL, Git, Heroku

Design/Other: Adobe: XD, Lightroom, Photoshop, Indesign, Illustrator, Affinity Designer, Microsoft Office Suite

AEC: AutoCAD, Revit, SketchUp, MicroStation, Bluebeam

Projects:

Chuck Roast

https://github.com/SamFan808/Chuck_Roast https://samfan808.github.io/Chuck_Roast/ HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery - group project, recipe app that queries a recipe API to provide a user with meal ideas

• Feed Your Bean

https://github.com/SamFan808/BeanTeam https://feed-your-bean.herokuapp.com/

MERN stack (MongoDB, Express, React, NodeJS - group project, full stack application that allows a user to continue their coding education through a selection of topical coding videos

• Discover Your Inner Animal

https://github.com/SamFan808/discover-your-animalhttps://sleepy-sierra-89293.herokuapp.com/

MySQL, Express,, JavaScript, HTML, CSS - group project, full stack application quiz that gives a user an experience to discover the animal inside through a series of questions

Experience

Shopworks Architecture / Architect

June 2017 - July 2020, Denver, CO

- Managed and completed production deliverables for affordable housing projects
- Maintained and implemented office-wide software (Revit) production and deliverable standards with an internal team
- Won the 2020 Housing Colorado Eagle Award for Indy Flats located in Lakewood, CO

Nest Architectural Design / Architect

October 2013 - September 2016, Denver, CO

- Managed and completed production deliverables for single family homes
- Maintained the client's vision and expectations to deliver a successful project in a timely manner

BurkettDesign / Architect

October 2011 - October 2013, Denver, CO June 2000 - February 2005, Denver, CO

- Managed and completed production deliverables for tenant finish and ground up projects, involving a wide range of clientele
- Maintained and assisted in office-wide software (Revit) production and deliverable standards

Education

University of Denver / Full Stack Bootcamp Certificate of Completion

Sep 2020 - March 2021, Denver, CO

University of Colorado @ Denver / Masters of Architecture

Aug 1998 - May 2000, Denver, CO

University of Colorado @ Boulder / Bachelors of Environmental Design

Aug 1991 - May 1995, Boulder, CO